<project>
  <Metadata>
    <metadata>
      <PackageName>Media Conversion Tool</PackageName>
      <Author>Sitecore A/S</Author>
      <Version>2.1.0</Version>
      <Revision />
      <License>&amp;nbsp;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;YOU SHOULD CAREFULLY READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS BEFORE USING THIS SOFTWARE (THE тАЬSITECORE SOFTWAREтАЭ). ANY USE OF THE SITECORE SOFTWARE IS SUBJECT TO YOUR FULL ACCEPTANCE OF THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT. ANY USE OF SITECORE SOFTWARE SIGNIFIES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT INCLUDING THE DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS CONTAINED HEREIN.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;License Agreement for Sitecore&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;License Grant&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Upon payment in full of the license fee, this License grants you a non-exclusive perpetual, limited, non-transferable, non-sub-licensable license to use the Sitecore Software on the following terms and conditions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;The license granted to You is for use of the Sitecore Software for Your internal business purposes only on the equipment, with the software features, and by the number and category of users paid for by You in advance of such usage (e.g. number of installations, storage options, CPUs, editors, web farms, etc).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;The Sitecore Software specifically may NOT be used in an ASP environment or similar environment which would in any way permit third parties to use the Sitecore Software.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;The Sitecore Software, the derivative works and improvements thereto and any and all worldwide right, title and interest in and to the Intellectual Property Rights to the Sitecore Software, including any documentation and manuals associated therewith, shall remain solely and exclusively&amp;nbsp; to Sitecore.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You will retain intact all applicable Sitecore copyright, patent and/or trademark notices on and in all copies of the Sitecore Software and any associated documentation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;For purpose of this license, тАЬIntellectual Property RightsтАЭ shall mean: (i) any and all patents, licenses, trademarks, service marks, trade names, trade secrets, know-how, inventions, copyrights and other intellectual property rights related to the authorship, origin, design, utility, process, manufacture, programming, operations or service of the Sitecore Software or documentation associated therewith; and (ii) any and all information relating to the Sitecore Software or such documentation not then generally known to the public.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;The Sitecore Software contains copyrighted and proprietary software. You may not (i) alter, modify, decompile, disassemble, reverse assemble or reverse engineer the Sitecore Software, including any database, file or library related thereto, (ii) give anyone else permission to modify the Sitecore Software (iii) distribute, sell, rent, assign, or otherwise transfer Sitecore software and documentation to third parties (iv) sublicense the Sitecore software or provide outsourcing, timesharing, rental or other such services to any third party.&amp;nbsp; You may not duplicate any Sitecore Software or the documentation associated therewith for any purpose.&amp;nbsp; All rights not expressly granted to You herein are reserved by Sitecore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Anti Piracy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;The Sitecore Software periodically transmits some or all of the following information only to a server located at SitecoreтАЩs headquarters: License key ID, licensee name, hostname (your website URL), host IP and directory installation path. This information is used solely to verify that the &lt;i&gt;license key&lt;/i&gt; is being used in authorized locations only. (You can turn off this feature by blocking outgoing HTTP connections from Your server).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Boost&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;The Sitecore Software may contain a feature allowing You on a limited basis to temporarily boost the number of simultaneous editors. Use of the feature will automatically be reported to Sitecore and you will be charged for use according to the current pricelist. Sitecore may at any time and for any reason disconnect the Boost feature.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Disclaimer of Warranty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;THE SITECORE SOFTWARE AND THE ACCOMPANYING FILES ARE SUPPLIED TO YOU "AS IS".&amp;nbsp; SITECORE MAKES NO WARRANTY WHATSOEVER AS TO THE SITECORE SOFTWARE, THE ASSOCIATED DOCUMENTATION, THE OPERATION OF THE SITECORE SOFTWARE OR ANY SERVICES RENDERED BY SITECORE TO YOU, WHETHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY, AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND ALL WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; IN NO EVENT WHATSOEVER WILL&amp;nbsp; SITECORE OR ANY OF ITS SUBCONTRACTORS OR LICENSORS BE LIABLE TO LICENSEE OR ANY THIRD PARTY (WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHER THEORY) FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SOFTWARE OR ANY PORTION THEREOF, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE LOSS OF USE OF THE SOFTWARE, INACCURATE RESULTS, LOSS OF PROFITS OR DAMAGES STEMMING FROM LOSS OR CORRUPTION OF DATA OR DATA BEING RENDERED INACCURATE, THE COST OF RECOVERING ANY DATA, THE COST OF SUBSTITUTE SOFTWARE OR CLAIMS BY THIRD PARTIES, EVEN IF&amp;nbsp; SITECORE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.&amp;nbsp; IN NO EVENT WILL SITECORE'S AGGREGATE LIABILITY UNDER THIS AGREEMENT EXCEED THE AMOUNT OF FEES PAID BY LICENSEE TO&amp;nbsp; SITECORE PURSUANT TO THIS AGREEMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Limitation of Liability&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;THE LIABILITY OF SITECORE IS LIMITED TO THE REPLACEMENT OF THE SOFTWARE OR THE REFUND OF THE LICENSE FEE PAID BY YOU. IN NO EVENT WHATSOEVER WILL SITECORE BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY (WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHER THEORY) FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, RELIANCE, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITECORE SOFTWARE OR ANY PORTION THEREOF, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE LOSS OF USE OF THE SOFTWARE, INACCURATE RESULTS, LOSS OF PROFITS OR DAMAGES STEMMING FROM LOSS OR CORRUPTION OF DATA OR DATA BEING RENDERED INACCURATE, THE COST OF RECOVERING ANY DATA, THE COST OF SUBSTITUTE SOFTWARE OR CLAIMS BY THIRD PARTIES, EVEN IF SITECORE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.&amp;nbsp; IN NO EVENT WILL SITECOREтАЩS AGGREGATE LIABILITY UNDER THIS AGREEMENT EXCEED THE AMOUNT OF THE LICENSE FEE PAID BY YOU FOR THIS LICENSE.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&lt;br clear="all"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Patent or Copyright Infringement &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;If any third party claim based upon alleged infringement of a patent or infringement of a copyright under the laws of the United States, Canada or the European Union is asserted against You by virtue of your use of the Sitecore Software, Sitecore will indemnify You in investigation of such claims, in preparation and in defence of such claims, or in settlement thereof, provided that Sitecore&amp;nbsp; shall have received from You notice of said claim within ten (10) days of the assertion thereof, and further provided that Sitecore shall have the exclusive right, if it so chooses, to control and direct the investigation, the defence or the settlement of such claim and further provided that Sitecore shall receive complete cooperation and assistance from You in defending or settling the claim. Sitecore shall have no liability for any claim of infringement based on: (i) use of a superseded or altered version of the Sitecore Software if the infringement would have been avoided by the use of a current unaltered versionrelease of such Sitecore Software; or (ii) the combination, operation or use of the Sitecore Software with any software, hardware or other materials not furnished by Sitecore if the infringement would have been avoided without combining, operating or using such Sitecore Software with such other software, hardware or other materials.&amp;nbsp; In the event the Sitecore Software is held by a court of competent jurisdiction to be, or is believed by Sitecore to be, infringing, Sitecore will have the option, at its expense, to: (i) modify such Sitecore Software to be non-infringing; (ii) obtain for You a license to continue using such Sitecore Software; or (iii) terminate the license for the infringing Sitecore Software and refund a portion of the license fees paid by You for such infringing Sitecore Software as calculated based on a pro-rated deduction over a five year period from the date of original delivery of such infringing Sitecore Software. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Source Code in Escrow&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Sitecore has placed in escrow the source code for the latest version of the Sitecore Software. Under certain circumstances, Sitecore Solution Partners have the right to access such source code according to the terms and conditions of the applicable Sitecore Solution Partner agreement. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Software Patches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Sitecore may provide software patches as it deems appropriate in its sole and absolute discretion. Software patches will often be provided in an effort to correct a specific problem. Software patches, if any, will be made available to You free of charge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;To the extent that operation of the Sitecore Software is affected by problems in standard software used in connection with the Sitecore Software, then updates to such standard software per SitecoreтАЩs specifications will be required and mandatory in order to solve these issues. This includes (but not limited to) Microsoft Internet Explorer, Windows and the Microsoft XML DOM object.&amp;nbsp; Sitecore can provide no guarantees that problems with such standard software will be corrected in part or at all, and even if such problems are corrected, that the corrections will be made in a timely manner. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Privacy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;In connection with Your use of the Sitecore Software, You shall ensure that You meet and comply with any and all applicable laws and other requirements with respect to the protection of individuals, including, but not by way of limitation, the processing of personal data. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&lt;br clear="all"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Injunctive Relief; AttorneysтАЩ Fees&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;The remedy at law for any breach or threatened breach of the Section titled тАЭLicense GrantтАЭ shall be inadequate, and in addition to any other remedy available at law, in equity or under this Agreement, Sitecore shall be entitled to seek injunctive relief. In any action or proceeding to enforce any of the terms or provisions of this Agreement or on account of the breach hereof, the prevailing party shall be entitled to recover its costs and expenses, including, without limitation, reasonable attorneyтАЩs costs and expenses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;Upgrade Agreement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;If You have paid for a current upgrade agreement, You are entitled to receive new versions of the Sitecore Software without having to make additional payments. Each new version is accompanied by release notes describing the general consequences of upgrading to the new version.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;New versions of the Sitecore Software may change its functionality. Such changes may occur for both specific implementations and in regard to integration with external systems. Upgrades may also change the user interface and minimum requirements with respect to hardware and software requirements (e.g. the Internet Explorer version).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;If You hold the license to one or more module(s) of the software (e.g. add-ons), Sitecore cannot guarantee that new versions of the Sitecore Software will synchronize with any or all of such modules.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;The installation of any upgrade to the Sitecore Software may be performed by You or Your Sitecore Solution Partner at your own expense and responsibility.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;The Upgrade Agreement does not include any support or consultancy services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;An Upgrade Agreement may be purchased when You purchase the Sitecore Software. The Upgrade Agreement will automatically be renewed annually unless You cancel it in writing by sending such cancellation to Your Sitecore Solution Partner at least two months prior to expiration of the applicable anniversary date of this License. The price for the annual renewal of Your Upgrade Agreement is 15% of the retail price for the Sitecore Software. Five (5) years after the date of this License and on each five (5) year anniversary thereafter, Sitecore may adjust the price for the annual renewal of Your Upgrade Agreement to 15% of the then current retail price for the Sitecore Software.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;If and when the Upgrade Agreement has been cancelled, You will no longer be entitled to receive new versions of the Sitecore Software without first making additional payments to Sitecore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span lang="DA"&gt;September 7&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, 2005&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</License>
      <Comment />
      <Attributes />
      <Readme>Media Conversion Tool module for Sitecore 7.x</Readme>
      <Publisher>Sitecore A/S</Publisher>
      <PostStep />
      <PackageID />
    </metadata>
  </Metadata>
  <SaveProject>True</SaveProject>
  <Sources>
    <xfiles>
      <Entries>
        <x-item>/App_Config/Include/Sitecore.Modules.MediaConversionTool.config</x-item>
        <x-item>/bin/Sitecore.Modules.MediaConversionTool.dll</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/debug/</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/UI/</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/UI/Controls/</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/UI/Controls/Images/</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/UI/Controls/Images/progress_bar.PNG</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/UI/Controls/Images/progress_border.PNG</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/UI/Controls/Styles/</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/UI/Controls/Styles/MediaTreeview.css</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/UI/MainPage.xml</x-item>
        <x-item>/sitecore modules/Shell/Media Conversion Tool/UI/Progress.xml</x-item>
      </Entries>
      <Converter>
        <FileToEntryConverter>
          <Root>/</Root>
          <Transforms>
            <InstallerConfigurationTransform>
              <Options>
                <BehaviourOptions>
                  <ItemMode>Undefined</ItemMode>
                  <ItemMergeMode>Undefined</ItemMergeMode>
                </BehaviourOptions>
              </Options>
            </InstallerConfigurationTransform>
          </Transforms>
        </FileToEntryConverter>
      </Converter>
      <Include />
      <Exclude />
      <Name>Imported Files</Name>
    </xfiles>
    <xitems>
      <Entries>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Media Conversion Tool/{D0028DC5-AD68-47E5-AF14-CFD7B7449A3C}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Documents and settings/All users/Start menu/Programs/Media Conversion Tool/{141A69BA-941D-44CD-B3E5-592EE27AB3C1}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/layout/Layouts/Applications/Media Conversion Tool/{E2C75B5A-12FD-4621-9DC9-01B2908D5A29}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Content Editor/Editors/Media/Media Folder/Buttons/Convert Media/{DD33386C-AF06-4C0C-9A4E-786B745876B0}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Content Editor/Ribbons/Contextual Ribbons/Images/Media/MediaConversion/{0C367244-CAF6-4CBB-A208-38CBB5D05FF8}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Content Editor/Ribbons/Contextual Ribbons/Images/Media/MediaConversion/Convert Media/{CF7E4616-A26C-41A0-AA23-5EB6FCCA5820}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Content Editor/Ribbons/Contextual Ribbons/Media/Media/MediaConversion/{CE80B618-25F5-482C-9577-3D4A04517C90}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Content Editor/Ribbons/Contextual Ribbons/Media/Media/MediaConversion/Convert Media/{893E4B8C-5F1C-4BCA-8A6C-01550DB19651}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Content Editor/Ribbons/Contextual Ribbons/Playable Media/Media/MediaConversion/{DC0AE1DB-88AF-40FE-AB86-135642243B74}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Content Editor/Ribbons/Contextual Ribbons/Playable Media/Media/MediaConversion/Convert Media/{6282DDA5-C615-478C-A978-D8A1DE3D40C0}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Content Editor/Ribbons/Contextual Ribbons/Viewable Media/Media/MediaConversion/{FEBDBC09-202A-4FEB-B2F6-CD0CF90780DA}/invariant/0</x-item>
        <x-item>/core/sitecore/content/Applications/Content Editor/Ribbons/Contextual Ribbons/Viewable Media/Media/MediaConversion/Convert Media/{4EF1301A-2EA2-40B9-841B-6A878B056155}/invariant/0</x-item>
      </Entries>
      <SkipVersions>False</SkipVersions>
      <Converter>
        <ItemToEntryConverter>
          <Transforms>
            <InstallerConfigurationTransform>
              <Options>
                <BehaviourOptions>
                  <ItemMode>Undefined</ItemMode>
                  <ItemMergeMode>Undefined</ItemMergeMode>
                </BehaviourOptions>
              </Options>
            </InstallerConfigurationTransform>
          </Transforms>
        </ItemToEntryConverter>
      </Converter>
      <Include />
      <Exclude />
      <Name>Imported Items</Name>
    </xitems>
  </Sources>
  <Converter>
    <TrivialConverter>
      <Transforms />
    </TrivialConverter>
  </Converter>
  <Include />
  <Exclude />
  <Name />
</project>
